freewordpresstheme.info 2009-12-12

# Privacy Policy | Free Wordpress Themes

## [Privacy Policy](http://www.freewpblogthemes.com/privacy-policy/ "Privacy Policy")

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our sites. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:

##### Log Files

Like most standard website servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, administer the site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

##### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Our site use cookies for tracking visitors activity. Some of my business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser's settings section.

##### Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. we encourage ours users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

##### Advertisers

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to these information. We work with the ad companies like Google Adsense and Amazon.

##### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, do not hesitate to [contact](http://www.freewpblogthemes.com/contact/ "contact") us via contact us page.

Thank you all
